reimagemac.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Reimageplus.com

This document explains the privacy policy and practices of Reimageplus.com, a web-based PC maintenance and repair service operated by Reimage Limited ("Reimage" or the "Service"). This Policy is part of the Terms of Service for using Reimage. This Policy was last updated on: 5/12/2015. At Reimage, protecting your personal information is an essential part of our Service. This Policy explains what personal information we collect from you, why we collect it and how we use it.

Reimage Limited has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us, at [about@reimageplus.com](mailto:about@reimageplus.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, http://www.reimageplus.com/ and does not cover information that may be collected through any software downloaded from this Web site.

### What Personal Information Do We Collect?

Personal information is any information that can be used to identify an individual, such as your name, physical address, contact information (e.g., email address, phone number), title, and occupation. 

To set up a free call with a PC expert, we ask for your name and phone number so that one of our PC experts may call you and walk you through the process of how our software works.

To list your business on our site we will collect the zip code, state, city and Name of the company. To remove yourself from our list you may contact us at [support@reimageplus.com](mailto:support@reimageplus.com) at any time.

To add a new location we will ask for your name and email address and location information of the business you wish to add a location for. We will ask for the name, address, phone number, fax number, email address and website of the business you wish to add.

### Online Registration Form

Our site may contain registration forms that require users to provide us with contact information form such as their names and email address. We use this information to send you news and updates and promotional material about our products or from some of our partners. We do not pass this information to third parties other than the people working with the product or website. Users may opt out of any unwanted emails by the remove option in the emails or by contacting us directly at [support@reimageplus.com](mailto:support@reimageplus.com).

### Subscribing to our blog

In order to subscribe to our blog we will ask for your email address, we use this information for the sole purpose of notifying you when we have posted a new blog or when someone has commented on a blog that you have commented on.

### Ordering our service

To order our service you must choose which option works best for you, once you click on order now you will be directed to our third party payment gateways domain. Although this page may have the look and feel of reimage.com please make sure that you are aware that you are now on our third party payment processor's site in order to complete your transaction. The name, card number, expiration date, and email address will be collected to process your request. Your name and email address will be shared back with us in order for us to provide you with your key to complete the process. We do not have any access to the credit card information you submitted to our payment processor. The payment processors privacy policy governs the collection and use of the information collected during the check out process.

We also collect technical information about your computer in order to carry out the ReImage Service. This includes your IP Address, browser type, Inventory Description File (which we create as part of the system scanning process) and your Customer Configuration. Your technical information is associated with your personal account. This information is used to understand what a correct configuration for your computer should look like, what your actual configuration contains, and what files we need to retrieve and install to repair your computer or to carry out other functions of the Service that you have selected. Note: We do not make copies of your program or data files on your computer to perform the Service.

### Why do we collect Your Personal Information?

We collect the personal information:

  * To conduct repairs and maintenance on your computer as requested by you
  * To perform archive and restoration activities requested by you
  * To locate and retrieve correct computer files from publicly available sites on your behalf
  * Participation in Discussion Groups
  * Newsletter subscriptions
  * Personalization of the user experience on Reimage
  * Scientific research and improvement of the Service
  * To notify you of our new services or changes to our existing Services
  * To send you technical or service-related communications
  * To enforce the Terms of Service

### How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

We will only use your personal information in the way that we described at the time of collection, including when you provide your information to download the free scan. We will not subsequently change the way your personal information is used without your consent. 

### Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information

You may access, change or delete your personal information by emailing us at [support@reimageplus.com](mailto:support@reimageplus.com). You may delete your account or unsubscribe from certain features (e.g., online newsletters) at any time by using the email address provided above. You may also unsubscribe from certain features such as emails or newsletters by using the "unsubscribe" function provided within each email notification or newsletter. Personal information relating to deleted accounts may be archived by the Service according to its normal backup procedures. The Service may retain your Inventory Description File and use it for research and system improvement purposes described in the Terms of Service. Certain information (e.g., online discussion forum postings) may continue to be displayed publicly even if you delete your account. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

### Sharing Your Personal Information

We do not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy. We may share certain personal information with trusted vendors to carry out a transaction you have requested (e.g., sharing card payment information with our credit card processor to obtain payment of fees and to activate your subscription to the Service). We use Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding your order. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes. 

We may collect and possibly share your personal information to enforce the Terms of Service. This may be done to prevent a crime or violation of our Terms or to help solve a transgression that has been committed. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. If Reimage is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

### Security of Your Personal Information

Reimage uses a combination of security features and techniques to safeguard and protect your personal information. For example, your credit card data is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology when transmitted to on our card processors site

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at [support@reimageplus.com](mailto:support@reimageplus.com).

### Tracking technologies

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you.

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Reimage and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference). Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as Flash to collect and store information.  
To manage Flash LSOs please click [here.](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html)

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

### Third Party Websites

Our Service may contain links to third party sites. We have no control over the privacy practices of these sites, so you should read their privacy policies to understand their practices. We do not endorse any third party sites. 

### Public Forum

If you participate in the blog offered on this site, remember that postings are public communications. Keep this in mind before posting a public message. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these blogs, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [product@reimageplus.com](mailto:product@reimageplus.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

### Customer Testimonials/Review

We post customer testimonials/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do not use any identifying information such as email or user ID on these testimonials, and the name is fabricated in order to protect the identity of our customers. Testimonials and user feedback are used sporadically in marketing materials, and are identified as a Reimage Customer. If you want Reimage to remove your testimonial, or don't want Reimage to use your testimonial in any marketing materials, then please write to: [about@reimageplus.com](mailto:about@reimageplus.com)

### Social Media Features and Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

### Children's Privacy

Our Service is not intended to be used by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

### Policy Updates

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective. 

Last update: 5/12/2015. 

### Questions or Comments?

Please send your question or comments to us at: [legal@reimageplus.com](mailto:legal@reimageplus.com)

Or to:

Reimage Limited  
Athinodorou 3  
Dasoupoli, Strovolos, Nicosia  
P.C. 2025  
Cyprus
